<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travel on Dileepsa</title>
    <link>https://dileepsa.github.io/tags/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travel on Dileepsa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 15:42:43 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dileepsa.github.io/tags/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Coorg</title>
      <link>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/coorg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 15:42:43 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/coorg/</guid>
      <description>Overview Coorg is located on the eastern slopes of the Western Ghats in Karnataka. With year-round pleasant weather, lush coffee estates and thick forests, it is one of the most sought-after hill destinations in India.
Day 1 Golden Temple Namdroling Monastery should be high up in your list of places to visit in Coorg. It is home to thousands of students (both monks and nuns) from the Tibetan community that live and study in these premises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kakinada</title>
      <link>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/kakinada/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 18:22:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/kakinada/</guid>
      <description>Little about kakinada A city with a perfect blend of cosmopolitan lifestyle and old-world charm, Kakinada in Andhra Pradesh is blessed with the best of both the cultures. One side showcases the rich cultural heritage, while the other side will leave you in awe of its success in industrialization and architectural grandeur.
My experience in kakinada Kakinada is a great place for nature lovers and history buffs. I always enjoy being in nature friendly places.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lepakshi</title>
      <link>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/lepakshi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 18:39:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/lepakshi/</guid>
      <description>Overview After tiring and prolonged work schedule for many weeks, we decided to head towards a place where we could score a completely new experience. We wanted a bike trip along with the experience. So we dediced to explore lepakshi.
The name Lepakshi formed from the union of two Telugu words Le &amp;amp; Pakshi – which means Rise &amp;amp; Bird respectively. As per the Ramayana Mythology Ram helped Jatayu to attain Moksha by uttering these two words.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pondicherry</title>
      <link>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/pondicherry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 07:20:39 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/pondicherry/</guid>
      <description>Pondicherry now known as Pudcherry. Pondicherry is a lively destination that offers everything - colonial architechture, pebbeled beaches, historic sites &amp;amp; heritage, a beautiful seaside prominade, and more
History and Culture Pondicherry was once the home for the French and they blended South Indian culture with their own unique tradition.
Therefore, the beautiful French Quarter in Pondicherry gives you a feel of Indian French culture as the portion of France still exists in India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Srisailam</title>
      <link>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/srisailam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 09:51:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/srisailam/</guid>
      <description>The second jyotirling of Shiva , named Mallikarjuna Swamy is located in Srisailam, Andhra Pradesh, also termed as Kashi of the South. It is located at a distance of around 268 kms from Vijayawada in Nallamala hill forests along the banks of Krishna river. The important attractions in the area include the Panchamathams, Sakshi Ganapathi, Sikharam and Srisilam Dam. The best time to visit Srisailam is the monsoon season when the forests are green offering spectacular views.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nandi Hills</title>
      <link>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/nandi_hills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 19:53:11 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/nandi_hills/</guid>
      <description>Nandi Hills, a small albeit beautiful town, is just 60 km away from the city of Bangalore and has emerged as the perfect weekend getaway for its people. Even though it is most well-known for its viewpoints and its greenery, Nandi Hills is also a popular historical fortress that is home to a number of temples, monuments and shrines.
How to reach The best way to reach the Nandi Hills is by taking a personal vehicle if you have limited time or seek comfort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bangalore Tour</title>
      <link>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/bangalore_tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 15:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/bangalore_tour/</guid>
      <description>Iskon Temple ISKCON Temple is known for its activities of engagement involving ardent devotees of Lord Krishna.
The architecture of Bangalore&amp;rsquo;s ISKCON temple is a magnificent presence and is credited to being the largest ISKCON complexes in the world.
The most distinctive feature of this temple is it&amp;rsquo;s gold plated flag post which stands at a height of 17 metres.
The main shrine which is also called the Rajagopuram has beautiful archways and water fountains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bannerghatta</title>
      <link>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/bannerghatta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:09:09 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/bannerghatta/</guid>
      <description>Located on the outskirts of Bangalore, and usually known as BBBP, the Bengaluru Bannerghatta Biological Park is amongst the most popular and frequently visited destinations in the city. Catering to nature and wildlife enthusiasts, it is an integral part of the magnificent Bannerghatta National Park and is spread across a massive area.
How to reach bannerghatta The Park is located 22km outside Bangalore City and can be easily reached using public transport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Araku</title>
      <link>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/araku/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 18:00:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/araku/</guid>
      <description>Araku Valley in the heart of Andhra Pradesh is undoubtedly a stunner. Araku Valley is one of the most spectacular vacation spots in the state of Andhra Pradesh. Surrounded by high mountains, lush green forests, foggy clouds, and a pleasing climate, Araku Valley is a perfect escape for those who are tired of living the monotonous life. The serene and tranquil environs not only calm your soul but also make your inner soul happy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysore</title>
      <link>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/mysore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 14:00:11 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/mysore/</guid>
      <description>Mysore city is located at the base of the Chamundi Hills and offers visitors a wealth of natural beauty that is matched only by its stunning architecture. With its namesake World Heritage-listed palace, peaceful yoga practices and intriguing heritage, it is no wonder that Mysore is South India’s most popular tourist destination.
How to reach If you are travelling from bangalore, try booking a cab from any travel agency. We booked a traveller and we are around 20 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Krishnagiri</title>
      <link>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/krishnagiri/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 10:25:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dileepsa.github.io/posts/krishnagiri/</guid>
      <description>Blessed with gorgeous natural landscape and an abundance of black granite, the city of Krishnagiri in Tamil Nadu is a must visit for a discerning traveller. The name Krishnagiri literally translates into &amp;ldquo;Black Hill&amp;rdquo; - &amp;lsquo;Krishna&amp;rsquo; meaning &amp;lsquo;black&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;giri&amp;rsquo; meaning mountain. Krishnagiri is very popular for its production of mangoes and hence its often termed as the Mangoes&amp;rsquo; Own Land.
Best Time to Visit Krishnagiri The best time to visit Krishnagiri is the winter season.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
